{"52012839":[{"question":"Ruby on Rails Undefined Method for simple_form_for","user":"XXXOMEGALORDXXX","score":15,"votes":1,"answers":1,"views":19,"language":"ruby"}],"52012956":[{"question":"Create site like feedly using ruby on rails [on hold]","user":"Adam Adam","score":1,"votes":-5,"answers":0,"views":31,"language":"ruby"}],"52013287":[{"question":"Many to many getting “is invalid” error in Rails","user":"Victor Luna","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":40,"language":"ruby"}],"52013542":[{"question":"I don't have a param key in my Rails Application. How do I either work around it or set one up so I ","user":"XXXOMEGALORDXXX","score":15,"votes":1,"answers":1,"views":20,"language":"ruby"}],"52013793":[{"question":"Rails multiple ruby processes on ec2 server causing 100\\% CPU utilisation","user":"Prem","score":970,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":22,"language":"ruby"}],"52014018":[{"question":"Ruby how to get 2018-08-25 from DateTime object?","user":"jdog","score":4,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":34,"language":"ruby"}],"52014744":[{"question":"Get full time zone name given an instance of ActiveSupport::TimeWithZone","user":"John","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":20,"language":"ruby"}],"52015631":[{"question":"Making leader board","user":"some thing","score":13,"votes":2,"answers":3,"views":36,"language":"ruby"}],"52016765":[{"question":"Fail of Deployment of Ruby on Rails App in Azure Web App Linux","user":"Michel Fernandes","score":23,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"ruby"}],"52017058":[{"question":"Can't get longitude and latitude in telegram-bot-ruby","user":"Bdabrowski","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"ruby"}],"52017164":[{"question":"using acts_as votabable gem for likes and want to change the heart color to red permanently after us","user":"Emanuel Coen","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":15,"language":"ruby"}],"52017726":[{"question":"Rspec not work post :create","user":"Артур Бунько","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":20,"language":"ruby"}],"52017970":[{"question":"Handling txt file and data structures","user":"Gerard22","score":24,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":34,"language":"c"}],"52018077":[{"question":"Solved — Scanning does not work properly - C","user":"user75283","score":1,"votes":-2,"answers":1,"views":46,"language":"c"}],"52018270":[{"question":"Rescue not capturing failure","user":"ToddT","score":604,"votes":0,"answers":2,"views":26,"language":"ruby"}],"52018280":[{"question":"C void pointer with ternary operator","user":"Wiktor","score":3,"votes":0,"answers":2,"views":49,"language":"c"}],"52018421":[{"question":"Requests from this ios client application <empty> are blocked","user":"Bartłomiej Semańczyk","score":31,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"ios"}],"52018458":[{"question":"Mailchimp subscribe modal / popup IOS portrait mode expanding","user":"user3260190","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":5,"language":"ios"}],"52018479":[{"question":"error for object 0x7faa4d081f98: pointer being freed was not allocated Ruby (ROR) malloc_error_break","user":"Wouter Schoofs","score":359,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":19,"language":"ruby"}],"52018505":[{"question":"Crashing on writing to realm database","user":"King","score":188,"votes":0,"answers":2,"views":18,"language":"ios"}],"52018661":[{"question":"Why my sticker doesn't work after (maybe)2 weeks?","user":"marko999","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":13,"language":"ios"}],"52018674":[{"question":"Reuse xib in different screens","user":"KukhtoA","score":30,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":23,"language":"ios"}],"52018773":[{"question":"fgets() initializes variables on its own","user":"InTheMoodForNow","score":19,"votes":1,"answers":1,"views":31,"language":"c"}],"52018778":[{"question":"Server/Client TCP sockets Terminal Window","user":"Wizard","score":137,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":15,"language":"c"}],"52018822":[{"question":"Explanations needed for this Pi computation [duplicate]","user":"Exho","score":94,"votes":-2,"answers":0,"views":24,"language":"c"}],"52018845":[{"question":"How to limit the internet traffic for 1 thread in iOS?","user":"Oleksandr","score":358,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":9,"language":"ios"}],"52018914":[{"question":"AndroidStudio : Donate Features [on hold]","user":"r.kuypers","score":1,"votes":-3,"answers":0,"views":13,"language":"ios"}],"52019014":[{"question":"Make keyboard disappear when clicking outside of Search Bar - SWIFT","user":"johnDoe","score":85,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":12,"language":"ios"}],"52019149":[{"question":"Conflict with a UIPanGestureRecognizer on a UITableView's superview","user":"Greg de J","score":91,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":10,"language":"ios"}],"52019153":[{"question":"I did not get how x=0 and y=6 came as output","user":"Jay Gupta","score":1,"votes":-1,"answers":2,"views":24,"language":"c"}],"52019169":[{"question":"Ruby on rails - each do class?","user":"flenning12","score":11,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":23,"language":"ruby"}],"52019179":[{"question":"Why address of static variable in one file is different when did a call from different points?","user":"user6468372","score":42,"votes":-1,"answers":0,"views":21,"language":"c"}],"52019255":[{"question":"array[x] assignment don't work in c [on hold]","user":"gabida.py","score":1,"votes":-5,"answers":0,"views":32,"language":"c"}],"52019386":[{"question":"How to subclass a Page Controller?","user":"Noodledew","score":5,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":9,"language":"ios"}],"52019429":[{"question":"C how to reliably keep track of multiple file pointers [on hold]","user":"PSP CODER","score":19,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":21,"language":"c"}],"52019486":[{"question":"UITextView keep scrolling to bottom - iOS","user":"Student","score":63,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"ios"}],"52019513":[{"question":"Regex capturing group not working as intended [duplicate]","user":"concuncan","score":14,"votes":2,"answers":1,"views":23,"language":"java"}],"52019541":[{"question":"pointerIndex out of range exception in photo editor","user":"Nithis Kumar","score":8,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"java"}],"52019572":[{"question":"Keep getting the java.util.NoSuchElementException on this program","user":"Jdawg32","score":16,"votes":0,"answers":3,"views":26,"language":"java"}],"52019577":[{"question":"How to use HTML in JTable custom renderer","user":"K. Wenzel","score":3,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"java"}],"52019590":[{"question":"possible outputs of code with fork()","user":"DonaldT","score":23,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":5,"language":"c"}],"52019607":[{"question":"How is C++ better type checked than C? [on hold]","user":"pasha","score":664,"votes":-2,"answers":0,"views":37,"language":"c"}],"52019614":[{"question":"plus 2 number == android studio","user":"Tohid Da","score":1,"votes":-2,"answers":0,"views":9,"language":"java"}],"52019618":[{"question":"Error executing DDL via JDBC Statement with Spring Boot default configuration","user":"stakowerflol","score":51,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":7,"language":"java"}],"52019627":[{"question":"Imagine this controlling Eclipse IDE using voice, is this good idea?","user":"Ivan Gavlik","score":1,"votes":-2,"answers":1,"views":13,"language":"java"}],"52019628":[{"question":"Copy pointer in C [duplicate]","user":"jonnyx","score":59,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":11,"language":"c"}],"52019644":[{"question":"Spring MVC - Override a bean for one Integration test","user":"MLem","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"java"}],"52019650":[{"question":"Static recursive [duplicate]","user":"fluffymoose","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":14,"language":"java"}],"52019653":[{"question":"Strange behaviour when using recursion in an if statement, inside a method. Java","user":"Picky Apothecary","score":1,"votes":-1,"answers":1,"views":31,"language":"java"}],"52019683":[{"question":"TrustKit with SHA256withRSA","user":"John","score":58,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":3,"language":"ios"}],"52019697":[{"question":"Move background view down with pull-to-refresh - swift","user":"Micro","score":5,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":7,"language":"ios"}],"52019727":[{"question":"Would java allow me to assign this object to this generic field?","user":"basin","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":17,"language":"java"}],"52019732":[{"question":"Getting error “org.springframework.web.servlet.DispatcherServlet noHandlerFound” in Spring MVC Proje","user":"user3244519","score":241,"votes":0,"answers":1,"views":13,"language":"java"}],"52019746":[{"question":"Callback function not reloading database","user":"King","score":188,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":10,"language":"ios"}],"52019800":[{"question":"Define the following modules to display the system’s summary.","user":"Deepak","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":5,"language":"c"}],"52019804":[{"question":"How to make fully filled in Cross star pattern as shown below?","user":"prashant balotra","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":9,"language":"java"}],"52019813":[{"question":"Filter the list of objects based on different conditions using Java","user":"Sid","score":11,"votes":-1,"answers":0,"views":12,"language":"java"}],"52019815":[{"question":"textField Editing Changed not reacting fast enough","user":"Bjorn Morrhaye","score":108,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":5,"language":"ios"}],"52019822":[{"question":"Labels in a loop and random numbers, please help, I tried every things","user":"Jonathan Hendrikus Bonda","score":1,"votes":0,"answers":0,"views":8,"language":"java"}]}